If you go from end to end, if a patient
calls in, they book an appointment, then
what happens [music] from there is they
have to get their insurance
verified. And then they book time with
the doctor, they they come and see the
doctor for the insurance companies. It's
a whole another whole another game
there. Um and then they submit the
claims. They'll probably get rejected
because the insurance companies in
America are not very good. Um they go
back and forth, they try to get paid,
it's 3 months later, they get their
money, and it's a huge lag time. And
then from there, they still have to buy
all the drugs ahead of time, so they
have to front a lot of the money.
[music] This is a huge problem in the in
the practice space. Um so, just dealing
with all those things like end to end,
like Nitra overall, we're dealing with
the the financial aspect of this. And we
also have the AI software that handles
the scheduling of the patients, the the
claims management um for the the
doctors, and also the insurance um
eligibility checks. So, it's like we're
trying to do all these things end to end
so that for them it's just very easy.
They just see this whole thing happen um
handled by Nitra's AI. As we're going
this fast, like what not to do is to
hire [music] fast. And then when you
hire folks, always hire for uh the
people not for the role. Always hire for
like intelligence and um people who can
have a wider range of doing things.
[music]
>> Well, I wouldn't say like a generalist,
but like they just have more agency.
They see a problem, even if it's not
fixed, they'll just fix it.
>> By themselves.
>> Yeah, yeah, yeah. But then I think these
kind of people are all quite hard to
find.
To hire.
>> Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's why it's hire slowly cuz it takes
time.